{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037723491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037723491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_k-y-ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037727110","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037727110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_t-l-y"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037730602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037730602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-k-m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037734325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037734325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_s-y-h"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037737870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037737870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_s-y-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037741345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037741345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_b-y-ch"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037744703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037744703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_z-y-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037749031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037749031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_i-y-m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037752164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037752164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-a-b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037755768","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037755768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_b-y-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037761530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037761530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_y_b-y-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037767833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037767832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_y_b-y-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037775444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037775444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_y_b-y-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037809459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037809459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_y_b-y-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037815950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037815949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_y_b-y-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037822376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037822376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_y_b-y-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037829100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037829100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" dfea6223-44bd-4bec-8187-a394f1bd2f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Y..Y.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.123"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_y_b-y-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037835623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037835623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 18738cce-5c99-4254-91aa-31bab64adb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037854646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037854645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 18738cce-5c99-4254-91aa-31bab64adb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037857268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037857267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 18738cce-5c99-4254-91aa-31bab64adb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037857354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037857353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 18738cce-5c99-4254-91aa-31bab64adb22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037865633","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037865633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_d-z-f"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037868837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037868837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_i-o-z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037872083","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037872083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_t-a-z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037875334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037875333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-g-h"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037878765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037878765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_h-a-z"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037881894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037881894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-t"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037884798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037884798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-w-k"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037888190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037888190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_ch-e-z"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037893408","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037893408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_m-o-z"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037898027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037898027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037903792","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037903791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037909250","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037909249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 495a0c73-8167-4b42-ade9-be50fca3f50b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037930682","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037930681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_z_r"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037937355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037937354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_k_y_z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037944005","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037944005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_g_h"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037950641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037950641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_g_p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037957284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037957283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_l_r"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037963958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037963958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_z_y"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037970602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037970602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_z_y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037977208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037977208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_l_z"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037983845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037983844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_ch_z"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549037990510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549037990509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_k_j_z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038003699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038003699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_k_j_z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038008860","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038008860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 16f80013-68d7-4951-a6d3-7bee296c06d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_k_j_z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038039504","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038039503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038048041","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038048041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038059299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038059299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038069660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038069660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038073652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038073652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038086175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038086175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038099697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038099697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038111677","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038111677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038123486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038123486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038135590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038135590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038146968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038146968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038157125","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038157125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038167422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038167422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038176248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038176248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_l"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038187176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038187176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038198198","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038198198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038209406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038209406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_o"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038221311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038221311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038232575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038232575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038240576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038240575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038250878","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038250878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038262591","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038262591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038277233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038277233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038286638","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038286638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038295025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038295025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038306448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038306448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038315628","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038315628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038324809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038324809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038333255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038333255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038342601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038342601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_v"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038349404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038349404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_v"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038357164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038357164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_v"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038363784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038363784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_v"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038372375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038372375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_w"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038380526","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038380526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038388851","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038388851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038399588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038399588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549038405271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549038405270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_191508"," gameId":" 3bbf592b-fbc5-40c7-b633-eb66f057f227"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}